♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we've got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we'll withstand it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko stronger after all ♪
(GROWLING)
(SCREAMS)
Who is that screaming!
(YELLS)
Oh. W-Well, you are.
(GRUMBLES)
Do you know what time it is!
Uh…5 o’clock in the morning?
Y-Yes, that’s right!
And this is the third night in a row
you’ve woken me up!
I have had it!
(SCREAMS)
Out of our way!
Don’t go in there!
There’s a huge wolf inside!
Oh, really?
Agh!
Huh?
A four-eyed wolf!
(LAUGHTER)
(MELANCHOLIC MUSIC)
It’s a shame you didn’t
dream about me, Aelita.
Because, you know me,
I’m a real dream come true.
More like a nightmare
to tell the truth, Odd.
These visions of yours
are becoming a real problem.
It all started at the Hermitage.
I think you should go back there.
What? Back to that old house?
I’m not sure if you remember, but last time
we were attacked by a cupboard,
a lamp, and a gang of forks!
I don’t like that place. It scares me.
We don’t have any choice, Aelita.
If we don’t do something,
your hallucinations could get worse.
Don’t worry. This time
we’ll be with you.
My legs are shaking.
What’s happening to me?
You’re scared. It’s nothing to worry about.
It happens to Jeremie all the time.
Come on. We’ll see who’s scared!
There! There!
Stay down, boy!
See? Everything is just fine.
(HOWLS)
(SCREAMS)
Aelita! Are you okay?
Yes. I mean, I think so.
Did you have another vision?
Yes, but it was different this time.
It’s as if something, or someone,
was leading me to…
There was something
in a tree! Like that one!
Huh?
Mister Pϋck!
So, to make a long story short,
Aelita’s never seen this toy gnome,
but she’s been dreaming about it for days
and she knows it’s called Mister Pϋck.
It’s not a gnome. It’s an elf.
Well, whatever it is,
this whole story is
definitely paranormal.
Well, Aelita! Still playing with dolls?
Sissi, give that back right now!
Go fetch!
(CACKLES)
Hey!
A bit of advice -- give me
that toy right now.
What toy? Heh!
Herb!
I dare you to take your
glasses off! Come on!
I got it!
Uh-uh!
What is all this noise about?
Okay, you can have it.
But only because it’s you.
Right.
Look at this triangle marked A, B, C.
The point I is in the middle
of the segment AB…
What’s this key doing here?
What do you think it opens?
I sure wish I knew, but
I have no idea at all.
Hey!
A locker! It’s the key to
a train station locker!
Jeremie?
I’m listening.
Um…a complex number
is called transcendent
only if the rational coefficient's
polynomial root is a polynomial zero.
Yes, indeed. That is the
Sierpinski-Mazurkiewicz Paradox.
But it is not the answer
to our problem, so zero.
(LAUGHTER)
Train 6537 leaving
on track 5. All aboard!
This is it.
Would you like to do the honors?
"F. H." What does that stand for?
Fuzzy hands? Fifty-cent hot dogs?
Fried hegg?
Egg doesn’t start with an H.
Just testing to see if
you were on your toes!
Oh, wow! Music!
Certainly not.
Let’s see what we
can come up with.
Franz Hopper’s diary!
Great!
Maybe we'll be able
to find out more
about the Hermitage’s
mysterious owner.
For sure.
But not right away --
everything is encrypted.
I’ll have to decode it first.
How much time do you need?
One? Maybe two hours?
More like one or two years.
(RADIO PLAYS)
Come on. Time to get up.
Mhhn. Just a little bit longer!
I’m gonna take a shower.
(UNNERVING MUSIC)
(BARKS)
GAAAAH!
Ulrich, you here?
Ahhg!
(COUGHS)
Jeremie! Jeremie!
Huh? What?
XANA's ghosts attacked us!
Me and Ulrich.
What?
Don’t worry. No harm done.
They ran away.
The superscan didn’t detect
any activated towers.
XANA’s attack failed.
That’s weird. XANA can posses
humans, but not you two.
It must have something
to do with sex appeal.
Yeah, right. I’m sure of that.
See you later!
Wha--gaaah!
Running is the noblest event in athletics.
Except maybe for the long jump.
Or the shot put, javelin,
high jump…pole vault.
Some of you may associate
running with cowardice.
As in running away.
Nothing could be
further from the truth
since he who runs well goes far!
(CHORTLES)
Jeremie!
Uh, let’s see how
powerful your strides are.
Hmph. For those of you
with short memories,
Let remind you that, uh…
What was I gonna say?
Uh, right.
Uh, may I remind you
that we start when I say go.
Not on "get set"
and not on "ready."
I mean, well, after "ready."
Get set is when I say "go."
Right.
Okay.
On your marks.
Get set.
Go!
Uhg! Ouch!
What now?
I twisted my ankle!
Yeah, of course you did!
You don’t get strong muscles
sittin' in front of a computer!
Herb, take him to the infirmary.
Jim…
Would you mind if Aelita
came with me instead?
Okay, whatever.
Go on, then.
Take him far away from me!
Jeremie? You’re not limping anymore.
Has your ankle stopped hurting?
Aah!
Gah!
(CELL PHONE VIBRATES)
Yumi.
Ulrich, I think Jeremie’s been
possessed by XANA!
Are you sure?
This morning, Odd and I
were almost possessed
by a couple of ghosts,
but they didn’t succeed.
Why would it work on Jeremie?
No idea, but I saw him
heading for the park lands.
Aelita’s in his arms.
She was unconscious.
Oh, no.
I’ll check the superscan.
Let’s meet at the factory.
Okay.
Pitiful!
A slug coulda made it around faster!
Ulrich, I’m counting
on you to raise the level!
Uh, okay!
But I’ve gotta go to
the restroom first.
Oh, and I gotta go too, Jim!
(SIGHS)
Okay, okay!
Make it snappy!
Right, which one of you wimps is next?
Sector One. The ice territory.
South-southeast.
Huh?
Yeah.
XANA's attacked!
We have to stop Jeremie, and fast, too.
Okay. We’re on it!
Jeremie!
Jeremie, no! Listen to me, please!
So, you going down, too?
Boy, it’s totally weird to be
fighting against Jeremie.
I mean I don’t want
to hurt him, but…
(WHIMPERS)
Heah!
Yeagh!
Agh!
(SCREAMS)
Hiyah!
Quick. We’ve gotta get to Lyoko.
Here.
These are the coordinates
of the activated tower.
You guys go ahead.
I’ll take care of him!
(GROWLS)
Okay! Over here, twinkle fingers!
I have a good feeling
we’re really gonna hit it off!
How are you doing, Aelita?
Think you can handle it?
I’m not as good as Jeremie at it.
The virtualization countdown
has been launched.
Look! There!
He who runs well goes far!
Is Odd the one who
teaches you nonsense like that?
No. As a matter of fact, it’s Jim!
Whoa!
I’m sure glad that post was
there and not my face.
Got any other tricks up your sleeve?
(THUNK)
Uh-oh! That wasn’t
very smart, was it?
Especially since you’re
the one who’s gotta fix it.
Keep your eyes open, huh.
We don’t have Jeremie to
warn us about monsters this time.
(RUMBLING)
Uh-oh. I don’t like the sound of that.
How can you have
a decent discussion
with someone who has
no sense of humor!
Oh, easy does it!
Hah ha! Not so clever now, huh?
Bloks!
Take this!
Aaaah! G-g-g-g-gaaah! Whoa!
Aah!
Yumi, protect Aelita!
I’ll take care of the bloks!
Right!
Triplicate!
Fusion!
Hey, sparky!
Scared of heights, huh?
O-Okay, so you’re not
scared of heights.
Nice one, Aelita!
I’m gonna knock your block off,
you dumb blockhead!
Sounds like you miss Odd!
Your jokes are worse than his!
That’s what I call a job--
Materialization Yumi.
Yumi.
Ulrich!
Hang on!
I’m coming!
Trangulate!
The scyphozoa!
Aelita!
Uh-uh!
It’s not nice to devirtualize
your best friends!
Super sprint!
Thanks, Ulrich.
No sweat.
Head for the tower.
I’ll take care of this overgrown bug.
Oh, never trust a guy with glasses.
Tower deactivated.
Well?
How are you feeling?
Ugh.
Strange.
I remember talking to Odd and Ulrich,
and then after that, nothing.
Just a black hole.
XANA took control of you.
He destroyed all of Franz Hopper’s CD’s.
Apparently he had a problem with his notes.
Whew.
What do you mean, “whew?” It’s a disaster!
No, it isn’t.
Last night, when I got back
from the train station,
I stopped in here and I copied the CD’s
onto a highly restricted access
part of the supercomputer.
I'm the only one who can access them.
You’re a genius, Jeremie!
Still, there’s something I don’t get.
Why couldn't XANA’s ghosts
take control of Odd and me
and have no trouble controlling Jeremie?
No idea.
I might have an explanation.
Apart from you, we’re all
used to fighting on Lyoko.
Maybe that gives us
more resistance to XANA.
Maybe.
But then how can we protect me?
Hmn.
I just might have the answer.
(SCANNER REVVING)
Ugh.
Well?
That’s the last time
I ever set foot on Lyoko!
Why?
Just because of a couple of megatanks?
It’s really just not my thing!
I’ll never be able to hack it!
You know, I think I’d rather
be possessed by XANA
than go back there.
I’ll keep on the lookout for ghosts, that's all.
Well?
What did he look like on Lyoko?
He looked…how--
how can I say this tactfully?
Ridiculous.
That’s the word.
(LAUGHTER)
Come on, Mister Pϋck.
Let’s go for a walk in the garden.
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED BY
REDDIT.COM/R/CODELYOKO